n2growth.com 2008-12-18

# Strategic Growth Consulting Services,Executive Coaching Services,Leadership Development Services,CEO Coaching, Executive Coaching, Branding and Strategic Growth Services

N2growth ("N2") registration forms request certain contact and profile information (same as user name, e-mail address, profession, and so forth). The requested information is required in order to receive N2 services. The required information is clearly marked as such on the registration page. N2 tracks the open-rates of our HTML e-mails and certain click behavior from those e-mails to help us identify which portions of our newsletters are most popular with our readers. N2 uses this information in the following limited ways: 

  * to provide relevant, personalized, targeted news and information via e-mail; 
  * to help target advertising messages included in our e-mail newsletters so that we are able to continue provide our service to you at no cost; 
  * to enable our customer service professionals to respond to your feedback. 

**Information Sharing**

No personal identification information is ever shared with any other partner organizations, advertisers, or any other third parties.

**Legal Information**

Although we do everything within our power to protect the privacy of the information provided by the users of our site, we do reserve the right to share user information in the event that it is necessary to comply with any subpoena, court orders, or other legal process.

Copyright © 2006 N2growth.  All rights reserved. Protected by copyright laws of the United States and international treaties. Use of N2 logo's, branding information, tag lines, white papers, articles, blog posts, newsletter and other intellectual property may only be used pursuant to the subscription agreement and reproduction, copying, or redistribution for commercial purposes is strictly prohibited without the express written permission of N2.

The N2 newsletter and certain blog posts and other electronic data contains links to third party Websites. The linked sites are not under the control of N2 and N2 is not responsible for the contents, advertising, products or any other materials or links contained in these linked sites. N2 provides these links only as a convenience, and inclusion of a link does not imply endorsement of the linked site by N2 or its affiliates.

Information, documents, and links included in N2 documents and content are provided "as is" without any warranty. While N2 uses reasonable efforts to include accurate information, it does not make any representation as to its accuracy or completeness. The material is available to users who utilize this information at their own risk and N2 is not liable for any damages arising from use of its content.

Privacy Policy

**N2growth respects the privacy of its web site visitors**

We believe that responsible use of the information you share with N2growth("N2") and any of its operating subsidiaries is of the utmost importance. The following guidelines have been created in accordance with the United States Federal Trade Commission guidelines and European Union Personal Data Protection Directive. As part of our ongoing effort to provide best in class venture growth solutions to you, the consumer, N2 has outlined the following information to address online privacy and consumer protection. 

**Visiting N2's Website**

In general, people may visit any of N2s web sites and access information while remaining anonymous and not revealing any personal information. In order to provide you with relevant, desired information concerning products or services, N2 will, at times, request information from you. Prior to collecting such information, N2 will explain the purpose for which the information will be used. Unless we specifically disclose it to you at the time of collection, N2 does not provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source, to any third party. N2's purpose for gathering the information is to understand you better and also to make you aware of new products or offerings in which you may be interested. Any time you provide us with information, you will be able to indicate whether you want to receive additional information from N2. N2 may use "‘cookie" technology only to obtain non-personal information from its on-line visitors to improve the on-line experience. If you do not wish to have a "cookie" set when visiting the N2 web sites, you may alter the settings in your browser to prevent them. You will then be alerted each time a "cookie" is being sought and opt whether or not you wish to allow one to be set. This alert will show you how the cookie is being used and how long the information will be retained. 

**N2  respects and protects your personal information**

N2 will take appropriate steps to respect and protect the information you share with us. Whenever you give N2 sensitive information (credit card numbers, for instance), N2 will take commercially reasonable steps to establish a secure connection with your web browser. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for marketing purposes. 

**Updating your personal information**

You can help N2 to maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying N2 of any change to your address, title, phone number, or e-mail address. 

**European Union Personal Data Protection Notice**

Any personal data supplied herein may be processed and recorded in one or more database(s) under the control of N2. The supplying of all data is optional. However, failure to supply data may result in limited access to this web site. This data is intended for use by N2, and its subsidiaries, for purposes of identification and authentication, direct marketing and online transactions. 

**N2  welcomes comments and questions on this policy**

N2 is dedicated to protecting your personal information. Due to the rapidly evolving nature of technologies used to communicate with you, N2 may occasionally update this policy. Notice of any revisions will be posted to this site. Any comments or questions regarding our privacy practices can be directed to our corporate offices.
